const STORE = [
    {
        question: "How long was the longest dinosaur ever discovered?",
        answers: [
        '120 feet',
        '70 feet',
        '150 feet',
        '100 feet'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '120 feet',
    },
    {
        question: "Most dinosaurs were ...?",
        answers: [
            'Carnivores (meat-eaters)',
            'Herbivores (plant-eaters)',
            'Omnivore (plant and meat eaters)',
            'Frugivore (fruit-eaters)'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Herbivores (plant-eaters)',
    },
    {
        question: "The biggest dinosaur skull ever found was the skull of the torosaurus, how long was it? ",
        answers: [
            '3 feet',
            '4 feet',
            '12 feet',
            '8 feet'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '8 feet',
    },
    {
        question: "The word \"dinosaur\" comes from the Greek words deinos and sauros which translates to:",
        answers: [
            'Ancient Warrior',
            'Terrible Lizard',
            'Giant Fish',
            'Secret Dragon'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Terrible Lizard',
    },
    {
        question: "What year was the first dinosaur fossil discovered and identified?",
        answers: [
            '1902',
            '1921',
            '1898',
            '1932'
          ],
          correctAnswer: '1902',
      },
      {
        question: "How long ago did dinosaurs become extinct?",
        answers: [
            '100 million years ago',
            '20 million years ago',
            '65 million years ago',
            '40 million years ago'
        ],
          correctAnswer: '65 million years ago',
      },
      {
        question: "How many dinosaur species have been officially named?",
        answers: [
            'Over 10,000',
            'Over 5,000',
            'Around 500',
            'Around 1,000'
        ],
          correctAnswer: 'Over 5,000!',
      },
      {
        question: "The smallest discovered dinosaur was the size of a ____?",
        answers: [
            'Frog',
            'Pig',
            'Chicken',
            'Rat'
        ],
          correctAnswer: 'Frog',
      },
      {
        question: "T-Rex teeth were the size of ____?",
        answers: [
            'an elephant Tusk',
            'a human hand',
            'a watermelon',
            'a car'
        ],
          correctAnswer: 'a human hand',
      },
      {
        question: "What are scientists who study dinosaurs and fossils called?",
        answers: [
            'Jurassicologists',
            'Fossilologist',
            'Dinologist',
            'Paleontologist'
        ],
          correctAnswer: 'Paleontologist',
      },
    ]